fisherpaykel.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Statement - Fisher & Paykel Appliances United States of America

### FPA Privacy Policy

Fisher & Paykel Appliances is committed to protecting your privacy and to giving effect to relevant privacy legislation. Most of our site can be accessed without the need to give us any information about yourself. The information below is designed to explain how we collect, use and protect any information you provide to us (if any) through the website.

### The information we collect

Fisher & Paykel Appliances collect general and statistical information from your computer when you browse through our website. This information does not identify you personally but is simply used to enable us to evaluate the performance of the website and allow us to assess statistical information on the overall experience of our visitors within our websites. 

At certain times we will request personal information from you in connection with online registration forms, product or service information or when giving comments or feedback on the site. The provision of the limited personal information requested is optional however failure to provide the necessary personal information when requested may result in certain services not being available to you. All personal information collected will be held by us and may be used by our employees, officers, agents, contractors and affiliates only for the purposes specified at the time of collection. Fisher & Paykel Appliances does not sell or disclose your personal information to other organisations without first informing you of such disclosures and, where required, obtaining your prior consent.

### The protection of your personal information

Fisher & Paykel Appliances is committed to protecting your privacy. We use a variety of technologies, systems and procedures to help ensure your personal information is protected from unauthorised use. We store your personal information in computer servers in controlled facilities and allow only authorised employees, officers, agents, contractors and affiliates to access this information. Although we make every effort to protect your personal information there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically. Your acceptance

By using our websites and submitting our online forms you are deemed to have accepted our privacy statement. Fisher & Paykel Appliances may make amendments to its privacy policy from time to time. You have the right to correct any personal information about you which we may hold or to have this information removed from our records. 

### Contact Us 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy please contact us through our feedback forms. If you would prefer to send your comments by mail please send to the following: 

Web Manager Fisher & Paykel Appliances Limited PO Box 58550 Botany, Manukau 2163 Auckland, New Zealand 

Click here to read our Disclaimer
